Farewell, Blue Cop
You can summon Mega Trucker any time you want with that card,
and you can give him commands, too.
Huh? What was that? What's going on out here?!
- Huh???
- Uh, Uncle Edo...
Stay away from Jun!
W-wait!
Uncle Edo, were you in the repair shop?!
I dozed off while working late... then I was woken up by a loud noise outside!
It was you! You were the one who broke my fence!
And ran over Jun's bike!
Aah, Uncle Edo, that's not what happened!
It's a misunderstanding, I-
Quiet, you! Don't come any closer!
What are you doing?
How dare you dodge that... you heap of scrap metal!
Please stop it. This is not safe!
What did you say?!
Please stop! Blue Cop isn't a heap of scrap metal!
He's from some planet called...
I am a Metal Cardbot. A mechanical lifeform from planet Machina.
Right, that's the one!
Why did you come to Earth? Are you trying to invade or something?!
No no no, sir! We are...
Hey, who are you calling, Edo?
I'm calling the cops, why? Do you think the army should be handling this?
T-that's not a good idea, sir!
Please, stop him, Blue Cop!
Right.
Ah, hello? Is this the army headquarters-
Waah!
Let me go!
You're just trying to threaten me to keep me quiet, aren't you?!
We have to clear up this misunderstanding somehow.
What should I do?
Just untie me already... my shoulders are killing me!
Blue Cop. Do something about his shoulders.
His shoulders?
Yes! Show him you're not a bad robot after all.
I heard on the radio that delivering a vibration of 3200 hertz helps blood circulation and relaxes the muscle.
Woah!
Ohh... that's good... that's the spot. Try to really get in there...
Ugh...
Are you alright?
No, I'm not... I'm tired and thirsty. Could you get me some coffee?
Yes, sir.
So you really can make coffee!
It's a basic skill for surviving on planet Earth.
One sugar and no cream, okay?
Yes, sir!
Here you are.
Augh, why is it so sweet?!
By one sugar, did you mean... one cube?
Are you trying to give me diabetes?!
Where are you going?
To work. I have a business meeting this morning that I have to prepare for.
And you! Make sure to get this mess cleaned up while I am gone!
Hey, kid!
You look like you need help. Want a hand?
This voice is from...
Mega Trucker?
Jun! Let's summon Mega Trucker!
Summon? You mean... bring him back out?
Yes. A Metal Cardbot that has been sealed cannot act against their master. In this case, you.
There's no need to worry.
Alright, I'll give it a try.
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
I may not look it, but such delicate work is my specialty.
Are you sure about that?
Leave it to me. Music START!
Mega Trucker, you're pretty good!
I'm just getting started!
Woohoo!
Stop it!
Don't get in my way! This is my favorite part!
Woohoo!
Aah! Both of you, knock it off! Stop fighting and start getting along!
...Did you guys finish clean-
WHAT IS THIS?!
What do you have to say for yourselves?
W-We're very sorry.
Oh, that's right! My meeting is starting soon.
I can't waste any more time.
And don't get into any more trouble while I'm gone!
Jun, don't you have to go to school too?
O-Oh, that's right!
Why is nothing going my way today!?
Looks like you need some help with that!
Blue Cop! I have a job for you!
So you can transform into a car.
Yes.
Wait...  so are all these cars friends of yours?
Huh?
There's a bad traffic jam.
Augh, but I'm in a hurry!
I'll do my best.
Wait, what are you going to do?
Woah, woah, woah! Watch out!
Oh!
Hang on, stop the car!
Come on, I said stop!
Police sirens should only be used in serious situations!
This wasn't one! And besides,
You aren't even a real police car!
...I'm sorry, sir.
Hmm... I have something important to discuss.
Uncle Edo! I'm back!
Oh, Jun! What's up?
Were you able to make it to the meeting?
Uhh... yeah.
What about Blue Cop?
You should just forget about that robot.
What do you mean?
I promise not to tell anyone about you. But in return, you gotta leave.
I can't do that! As you know, Jun has the Metal Breath, sir. Without Jun-
That's not my problem!
If something happens to Jun, how will I explain it to his parents?
So, you should leave. Go back to your own planet!
Edo, how could you be such an idiot?!
Huh? What's gotten into you?
Planet Machina was blown up in an explosion! Blue Cop has no home to return to!
Huh... what?!
If he had no home to go back to, he should have said that in the first place!
That truck seems to be a little wobbly, isn't it?
Coming through!
Ugh...
That was the wobbly truck!
Oh man... was the driver dozing off?
Oh no! We need to go alert the train, quick!
Blue Cop... where are you?
You wouldn't mind if I used the siren in this situation, would you?
Blue Cop!
Yes! Awaiting your command!
We gotta push that truck out of the crossing!
Yes!
Hey, stop the train! Please stop! C'mon, stop!!
This isn't working. I'm not strong enough on my own.
Hey, Jun!
Mega Trucker!
Looks like an emergency. Need a hand?
I could use one.
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Scoot over. I'll help you with that!
Just a little more!
Now!
So you spent thousands of years wandering the universe until you finally landed here on Earth?!
Okay... from now on, planet Earth will be your new home.
Really?
I'm sure we will need your help in the future.
Don't worry, I'll take good care of you guys!
Planet Earth is...
...our new home?
Here, you can wipe your tears with this.
Eugh...